statout.com 2018-05-15

# Privacy - statout

The privacy of our visitors to statout is very crucial to us.

At statout, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit statout, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

####  Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

####  Cookies and Web Beacons

statout does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

####  Special Note About Google Advertising

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services.

####  Policy Changes

statout reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, and will post any revisions on the Site. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy was last revised December 23, 2012.
